Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
=Vengeful Wife=
=Episode 19=
Men
are all the same.
But why can't I
remember last night clearly?
You're awake.
You didn't leave.
Since you're awake,
have breakfast.
(What's going on?)
(Didn't Ye Dong and Bai Cha
catch him red-handed?)
(I'm so charming!)
(It didn't take much effort to get him.)
(He even made me a hearty breakfast.)
Last night my wife came
to catch me red-handed.
Ye Dong set me up, right?
No need to deny it.
I've figured it out.
But
I never expected
you'd sacrifice yourself
for him.
What do you mean?
Let me put it bluntly.
I hate beating around the bush.
I prefer
laying all cards on the table.
My marriage is over,
because Ye Dong is always interfering.
To be clear,
I'm a plastic surgeon.
I can't resist
any beautiful things.
You're the most
gorgeous girl
with a perfect figure.
Actually,
your appearance
draws me in.
But
as you're working for Ye Dong,
you must be materialistic.
What are you implying?
This card has 10 million.
My plastic surgery hospital
has annual revenue in millions.
Stay with me,
and all this
will be yours.
What?
Trying to retaliate?
Your tricks won't work on me.
The money in this account
can be transferred to you immediately.
My hospital
can also be under your name.
Besides,
Ye Dong is a madman.
No woman
genuinely likes him.
You want to help him.
What price should you pay
to keep helping him?
Stay with me,
and all
this fortune
will be yours.
No.
More than a madman,
he's a demon.
If I betray him,
he'll kill me.
I can help you escape him.
Then you'll have
true control of your life.
What do you mean?
How can you help me?
I have my ways.
Eat first.
I'm afraid
you'll lose your appetite.
Explain yourself.
Make it clear.
How did you get this?
What's your goal?
Master,
have breakfast.
Thank you.
Master,
today's breakfast
comes with explosive side dishes.
What is it?
You told us to monitor Ye Dong.
Last night,
he took Bai Cha to a hotel
to catch
Cheng Nuo and Qin Yufei red-handed.
Qin Yufei?
Jiuyao's new CFO?
This matter
is quite intriguing.
Exactly.
Bai Cha stormed off in anger right then.
What's more infuriating
is that Cheng Nuo didn't come after her.
He stayed at the hotel all night.
What a scumbag.
But Ye Dong
was after Bai Cha all the way.
At last, Bai Cha told him
if he can make her
Jiuyao Group's CEO,
he will have a chance.
Bai Cha made us speechless.
Exactly.
Jiuyao Group is
a prominent group after all.
Can anyone become its CEO?
If she wanted material gains,
she could've asked for money
or asked Ye Dong to marry her.
But she wanted
the impossible position.
Even if she becomes CEO,
can she lead the group?
If she can't,
she'll
face ridicule
and unbearable pain.
Maybe she made up some excuse
to refuse Ye Dong.
But why this one?
It doesn't sound like an excuse,
but more like...
Like what?
Premeditation.
Good morning.
Have you washed up?
Yes.
Come and eat.
Thanks, Mom.
I don't know
where Cheng Nuo went last night.
His phone's turned off.
Mom,
Cheng Nuo is an adult.
Stop worrying about him.
Not him,
but you.
Eat the egg.
As your husband,
he stayed out all night
with his phone off.
Utterly disgraceful.
When he comes back,
I'll teach him a lesson.
Mom,
thank you.
Once I lived
in constant underworld
and surrounded by demons
who desperately wanted to consume me.
So
I tried to escape.
I ran for my life.
Finally, one day
I broke free from that underworld.
But along the way,
I met someone.
I thought he
desperately needed my help.
Yet because of him,
I got back into the underworld.
I truly believed
after that,
I'd not see light again
or trust anyone again.
What's going on?
Bai Cha,
why are you crying?
What underground?
What demons?
You don't mean Cheng Nuo, huh?
Did he do something to hurt you?
When he gets back,
I'll beat him.
You're a wonderful girl,
yet he doesn't appreciate you.
Let me
apologize on his behalf.
Don't cry now.
Mom,
thank you.
I hope you'll always
stay happy
and healthy.
I'll always remember you.
Let's eat.
It's delicious.
What exactly happened?
Tell me.
I'll take care of it for you.
Can't you stay?
Bai Cha,
remember to come back early.
You have my number.
Remember to call me.
Just
call me.
I bought Yunwu Manor for you.
Today I'm taking you there.
I'm not going.
What's wrong?
Don't you like it?
Where to live?
Do you know
who I hate the most?
Cheng Nuo?
Or
me?
So who is it really?
Lin Xia.
Then now
I know where you want to live.
But
my mother is living there.
Isn't that perfect?
When you're busy,
I'll help take care of her.
Okay.
♪Like a forgotten flower♪
♪Silently scattered across the horizon♪
♪Bathed in silent starlight♪
♪One day it will bloom♪
♪Let time heal the wounds♪
♪Clench the trembling hands♪
♪Embrace the faith of rebirth♪
♪The ending won't come too late♪
♪Under the mask♪
♪Observing all truths and lies♪
♪Who can see my strength♪
♪Tears soak my face♪
♪Under the mask♪
♪Seeking light in the darkness♪
♪What couldn't be let go♪
♪Eventually turns to dust in the wind♪
♪Under the mask♪
♪Observing all truths and lies♪
♪Who can see my strength♪
♪Tears soak my face♪
♪Under the mask♪
♪Seeking light in the darkness♪
♪What couldn't be let go♪
♪Eventually turns to dust in the wind♪